[
  {
    "episode": 1,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "NBA 2K25 features our _ season?", "answer": "11th" },
      {
        "question": "What position will you choose for your first build?",
        "answer": "Any (2KTV Clothing Item)"
      },
      { "question": "Chris returns as the head of which Affiliation?", "answer": "Elite" },
      {
        "question": "Which mode are you most excited to check out?",
        "answer": "MyCareer (100 VC)"
      },
      { "question": "Which WNBA player is a cover athlete for NBA 2K25?", "answer": "A'Ja Wilson" },
      {
        "question": "Which attribute category are you most excited for in MyCareer?",
        "answer": "Any (2KTV Clothing Item)"
      },
      { "question": "How many Streetball courts are in The City?", "answer": "3" },
      { "question": "What is your resolution for NBA 2K25?", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "There's a new game mode in NBA 2K25 MyTeam called?", "answer": "Breakout" },
      { "question": "Which MyTeam mode is not new in NBA 2K25?", "answer": "Salary Cap" },
      { "question": "In NBA 2K25, MyTeam and MyCareer have shared progression", "answer": "True" },
      {
        "question": "Who is the cover athlete of the NBA 2K25 Hall of Fame Edition?",
        "answer": "Vince Carter"
      },
      { "question": "On a scale of 1-10, how excited are you for NBA 2K25?", "answer": "Any" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 2,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which segment of the show are you most excited to watch this week?",
        "answer": "Any"
      },
      { "question": "What kind of games can you play at these Beach Courts?", "answer": "3v3" },
      {
        "question": "What year did Dr. James Naismith invent the game of basketball?",
        "answer": "1891"
      },
      { "question": "The new Badge Tier in NBA 2K25 is", "answer": "Legendary" },
      {
        "question": "Performing a Go-To Shot requires holding __ on the right stick.",
        "answer": "Up"
      },
      { "question": "What Block rating did you give your MyPlayer?", "answer": "Any" },
      {
        "question": "Performing a Floater or Runner requires holding __ on the right stick.",
        "answer": "Down"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many Streetball Bosses are waiting for you at each Streetball Court?",
        "answer": "8 or 9"
      },
      { "question": "What year did Vince Carter win the NBA Slam Dunk Contest?", "answer": "2000" },
      { "question": "Which MyTeam mode are you playing the most?", "answer": "Any" },
      {
        "question": "Which Celtics Evolution Card is the Level 10 MyTeam Reward in Season 1?",
        "answer": "Jaylen Brown"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 3,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Which segment of the show are you most excited to watch?", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Select your 2KTV top play of the week.", "answer": "Any" },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the new, highly-competitive mode in The City?",
        "answer": "Proving Grounds"
      },
      {
        "question": "Including Legendary, how many Levels of Badges are in NBA 2K25?",
        "answer": "5"
      },
      { "question": "How Many Levels of Takeover can you unlock in MyCareer?", "answer": "5" },
      { "question": "The rotating Badge Perk for Season 11 is called __.", "answer": "Synergy" },
      {
        "question": "Which new Badge increases the ability to Block or Contest the rim?",
        "answer": "Paint Patroller"
      },
      {
        "question": "You can complete the Rebirth Quest when your Build reaches __ overall.",
        "answer": "90"
      },
      {
        "question": "__ increases Defense of Post Moves and chances of Post Steals.",
        "answer": "Post Lockdown"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 4,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Rise" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Rebound" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Deadeye" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "99" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Mini Marksman" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Learn 2K" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "False" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "Any" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 5,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "What Year did Proving Grounds debut in NBA 2K?", "answer": "NBA 2K25" },
      { "question": "Proving Grounds features 5 different game modes to play.", "answer": "False" },
      { "question": "How often do you play games at Proving Grounds?", "answer": "Any" },
      {
        "question": "Clutch Time and Triple Threat can both be played in Breakout.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "You can choose which hand to try a layup with by using __.",
        "answer": "Right Stick"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Badge increases your ability to finish Alley-Oops?",
        "answer": "Aerial Wizard"
      },
      { "question": "Which play are you voting for?", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "What was your favourite segment of the show this week?", "answer": "Any" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 6,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "NBA 2K25 is the first NBA 2K to feature Press Conferences in The W.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "You can earn Goat Points in The W, and check your Career Progress in __.",
        "answer": "Pursuit of Greatness"
      },
      { "question": "A'ja Wilson recently won her __ WNBA MVP Award.", "answer": "3rd" },
      { "question": "How many Casual Courts are found in each Affiliation?", "answer": "One" },
      {
        "question": "Which Franchise will be making their WNBA Debut next season?",
        "answer": "Valkyries"
      },
      { "question": "Which spin do you think should win?", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "What was your favourite segment of the show this week?", "answer": "Any" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 7,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Victor Wembanyama" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Tyrese Maxey" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Stephen Curry" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "298" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "Brad Stevens" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Nikola Jokic" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "3" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "Rudy Gobert" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "4" },
      { "question": "Question 11", "answer": "Thunder" },
      { "question": "Question 12", "answer": "Mark Daigneault" },
      { "question": "Question 13", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 14", "answer": "Mike Conley" },
      { "question": "Question 15", "answer": "Naz Reid" },
      { "question": "Question 16", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 17", "answer": "Halloween" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 8,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "3" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Magic" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "554" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Magic" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "The Long Night" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "False" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Jonquel Jones" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 11", "answer": "Mexico" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 9,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "2K Beats" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Rebound" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "Home" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 10,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Backstory" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Ex-Coach" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "20" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "12" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Any" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 11,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "36" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "2K Share" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "MyGM" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "1" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "A-" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "Winner Takes All" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "The Steph Era" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 12,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "NBA 2K23" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "4" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "14" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Derrick Rose" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Perks" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Cavaliers" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 13,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "2021" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "4th" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Golf" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "Benny The Bull" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 14,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "2K Beats" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Season" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Russell Westbrook" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "All of Them!" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 15,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Pro-Am" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "15,000" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Jamal Murray" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "Carmelo Anthony" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Alter Ego" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "4" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 16,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Bucks" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Bulls" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Derrick Rose" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Chris Paul" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "A Mini Tournament" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "2" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "False" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Rudy Gobert" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 11", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 12", "answer": "Thunder" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 17,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Elite" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "10,000,000" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "False" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "5" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "Left Bumper" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Right Bumper" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Squads" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "Rebound" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "January 10" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 18,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Shai Gilgeous-Alexander" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Go The Gorilla" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "40" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Dwyane Wade" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "Doug Christie" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 19,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Trades" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Online" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Point Guard" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "0-3" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "40" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "3" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Cavaliers" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Thunder" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "D" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "Elite" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 20,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Zion Williamson" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "2KTV Builds" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "2" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Spurs & Pacers" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "2020" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "Banana Man" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 21,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "1985" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "$5000" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "3-Point Percentage" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Point Guard" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Third" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "9" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "Paris" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Cavaliers" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "2" },
      { "question": "Question 11", "answer": "Giannis" },
      { "question": "Question 12", "answer": "21" },
      { "question": "Question 13", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 14", "answer": "54" },
      { "question": "Question 15", "answer": "Players" },
      { "question": "Question 16", "answer": "2" },
      { "question": "Question 17", "answer": "True" },
      { "question": "Question 18", "answer": "1988" },
      { "question": "Question 19", "answer": "1997-98" },
      { "question": "Question 20", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 21", "answer": "San Francisco" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 22,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "2000" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Center" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Animations" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Cavaliers" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "LeBron James" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "6" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "LeBron James" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "True" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 23,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Victor Wembanyama" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Heat" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Triple Threat" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "OGs" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "Learn 2K" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "1" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Dyson Daniels" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "Tyler Herro" },
      { "question": "Question 11", "answer": "Mac McClung" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 24,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "30" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Celtics" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Hakeem Olajuwon" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Titanium League" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "False" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 25,
    "questions": [
      { "question": "Question 1", "answer": "Any" },
      { "question": "Question 2", "answer": "LeBron James" },
      { "question": "Question 3", "answer": "Balance" },
      { "question": "Question 4", "answer": "Boxout Beast" },
      { "question": "Question 5", "answer": "Nikola Jokic" },
      { "question": "Question 6", "answer": "False" },
      { "question": "Question 7", "answer": "The Kobe Era" },
      { "question": "Question 8", "answer": "Rebounding Champion" },
      { "question": "Question 9", "answer": "25.5" },
      { "question": "Question 10", "answer": "2014" }
    ]
  }
]
